if everybody could just please take your
如果每个人都可以请你
seat over there it's always intimidating
坐在那边总是令人生畏
to do a talk and incredibly huge room
进行演讲，并拥有巨大的空间
with a relatively small audience but all
受众相对较小，但所有人
right so so the last time I gave a talk
对，所以我上一次演讲
at a clips con it was just as Java 7
在短片上就和Java 7一样
launched and I did a talk 55 new things
推出了，我讲了55个新事物
in Java 7 and I did it in 55 minutes and
在Java 7中，我在55分钟内完成了
so I guess I didn't realize but you
所以我想我没意识到但是你
don't get 55 minutes anymore right
不再有55分钟了
there's been deflation in speaking time
说话时间里放气
so we have 35 minutes 34 now actually
所以我们现在有35分钟34
yeah so I submitted the abstract and you
是的，所以我提交了摘要，而你
know full disclosure I submitted the
知道我提交的完整披露
abstract for this talk before we had
我们之前的这次演讲的摘要
made several announcements about release
发布了一些关于发布的公告
cadence and Oracle building open JDK
节奏和Oracle构建开放式JDK
binaries and there's been a few other
二进制文件，还有其他一些
things happen over the summer with the
事情发生在夏天
intent of largely talking about that
打算大谈这一点
kind of stuff and luckily everything
一种东西，幸运的是，一切
happened and the abstract still kind of
发生了，抽象仍然是
holds but the abstract it was a little
持有，但摘要有点
vague but I made sure that it could it
含糊不清，但我确定可以
could cover this if there's something
如果有东西可以覆盖这个
that I mentioned in the abstract that I
我在摘要中提到的
didn't hit hard on the head before you
在你之前没有用力击打头部
just come up after and I'm happy to talk
刚来之后，我很高兴说话
about it offline also if you're gonna
离线也可以
have questions please come up to the
有问题请提出
front because I'm I'm sort of hard of
前线，因为我很努力
hearing all right
没事
this is our safe harbor statement if any
这是我们的安全港声明（如果有）
of you are Oracle customers I you know
你们当中有Oracle客户，我知道
when we put up a safe harbor statement I
当我们发表安全港声明时，我
always like to point out that Oracle's
总是喜欢指出Oracle的
safe harbor statement is way better than
安全港声明比
IBM's safe harbor statement
IBM的安全港声明
all right so first thing I want to do is
好的，所以我要做的第一件事是
and I'm always amazed how many people
我总是很惊讶有多少人
who are especially in the application
谁特别在应用中
development side of things I know a lot
开发方面我很了解
of people you're more on the tool side
的人，您更在工具方面
platform developers but I'm always
平台开发人员，但我总是
amazed that how easily confused people
感到惊讶的是，人们多么容易困惑
can get over JVM JRE and JDK and what is
可以克服JVM JRE和JDK，什么是
each and when we say Java SE what do we
每当我们说Java SE时，我们该怎么做？
even mean so when we talk about Java SE
甚至意味着当我们谈论Java SE时
we're talking about the whole technology
我们正在谈论整个技术
that's covered through the JCP through a
通过JCP涵盖了
specification all right so we're talking
规范好了，所以我们在说
when we say Java C we mean everything
当我们说Java C时，我们的意思是一切
but Java SE is composed of a few key
但是Java SE由几个关键组成
elements so the first thing that we like
元素，所以我们喜欢的第一件事
to talk about is the JVM and so you may
谈论的是JVM，所以您可能
know of the JVM as hotspot you may know
知道JVM是您可能知道的热点
if the JVM is je rocket which was from B
如果JVM是来自B的je火箭
EA but then is has been merged into
EA，但随后已被合并为
hotspot you may know if the JVM is open
您可能知道JVM是否打开的热点
j9 or j9 from IBM but basically the JVM
来自IBM的j9或j9，但基本上是JVM
is is the the process that runs on the
是在上运行的过程
hardware right so there's usually a
硬件对，所以通常有一个
specific JVM for a particular chipset or
特定芯片组的特定JVM或
operating system or combination thereof
操作系统或其组合
so it's the thing that's connecting the
因此，这就是连接
byte codes to to the bare metal and on
字节码到裸机上
top of that we have a JRE and the JRE
最重要的是，我们有一个JRE和JRE
has a JVM of course but it also comes
当然有一个JVM，但它也来了
with the standard libraries so libraries
与标准库，所以库
for doing all of the input/output or
用于完成所有输入/输出或
graphical things or you know networking
图形化的东西，或者你知道网络
collections etc etc many vendors will
收藏品等，许多供应商会
also include in their JRE some
在他们的JRE中也包含一些
additional things like maybe a browser
其他功能，例如浏览器
plug-in that can launch an application
可以启动应用程序的插件
either via applet or web start or you
通过applet或网络启动，或者您
know some other separate bits and pieces
知道其他一些零碎的东西
and then we have the JDK and the JDK
然后我们有JDK和JDK
comes with a JRE which comes with a JVM
带有JVM附带的JRE
and it includes developer tools right so
它包括开发人员工具
the most obvious is the compiler
最明显的是编译器
so Java compiler but also there's lots
Java编译器也有很多
of other tools in there like Java doc or
那里的其他工具，例如Java doc或
J shell or you know other pieces so
J shell或您知道其他内容
that's just a little bit of
那只是
disambiguation of the different bits
消除不同位的歧义
there so now let's talk about open JDK
在那里，现在让我们谈谈开放的JDK
so for those of you that maybe haven't
所以对于你们中那些可能没有的人
been involved you know like there's a
参与其中，你知道就像有一个
bunch of people here who obviously are
这群人显然是
you know day to day and open JDK but for
您知道每天都打开JDK，但是对于
those of you that may not be involved
你们那些可能不参与的人
this is where since 2006 we work in the
自2006年以来，这就是我们在
open-source implementation of Java C and
Java C的开源实现和
for the longest time until very recently
最长的时间直到最近
from an Oracle point of view from a sun
从甲骨文的角度来看
point of view we we had always thought
我们一直以为的观点
of open JDK as a place not a thing right
JDK开放作为一个地方不对
so it was a place where we collaborated
所以这是我们合作的地方
on source code to build open source
在源代码上构建开源
implementations of Java SE however
但是，Java SE的实现
recently and I'll get into this in a bit
最近，我会稍作讨论
we do think of it more of a as a thing
我们确实将它更多地视为一件事情
now where we will start to produce open
现在我们将开始生产开放
JDK binaries and builds from Oracle in
JDK二进制文件和Oracle中的构建
addition to the many that are long
除了很多长
existing and start thinking and
存在并开始思考
positioning open JDK in the ecosystem as
将开放JDK在生态系统中定位为
a thing not as a place so just a quick
一件事不是一个地方，所以只是一个快速
history on open JDK it's been around for
关于开放JDK的历史
a long time right so I know and again
很长一段时间，所以我知道又一次
especially with application developers
特别是对于应用程序开发人员
they don't really think about open JDK
他们真的不考虑开放JDK
that much because they just want to get
那是因为他们只想得到
the Oracle JDK downloaded use it build
下载的Oracle JDK使用它构建
their applications and forget all that
他们的应用程序而忘记了所有这些
other stuff that's what that's what
其他的东西就是那个
other vendors do that's what you know
其他供应商所做的就是您所知道的
Oracle and Red Hat and IBM and others do
Oracle和Red Hat以及IBM和其他公司
but yeah but but again it has been
但是是的，但是再次
around for a very long time it's been
已经有很长一段时间了
around since 2006 so that that means it
自2006年以来，所以这意味着
was launched by Sun Microsystems Red Hat
由Sun Microsystems Red Hat推出
was there at the very beginning Red
一开始就在那里Red
has always been and continues to be a
一直并将继续是一个
fantastic contributor and participant in
杰出的贡献者和参与者
in OpenJDK and they show a lot of
在OpenJDK中，它们显示了很多
leadership there they were the first to
他们在那里的领导
do builds of OpenJDK and they continued
做的OpenJDK的构建，他们继续
to produce high quality builds that are
生产高品质的建筑
distributed through through rel and
通过rel和
through through other distribution
通过其他分配
mechanisms Oracle itself until recently
机制直到最近
has redistributed Red Hat's builds of
重新分发了Red Hat的版本
open JDK yeah so that so again that this
打开JDK是的，所以再次这样
has been going on since 2006 now
自2006年以来一直在进行
obviously Oracle Sun and now Oracle
显然是Oracle Sun，现在是Oracle
we're producing the Oracle JDK or the
我们正在生产Oracle JDK或
Sun JDK and that was their first and
Sun JDK是他们的第一个
foremost thing but in the cases where
最重要的是，但在某些情况下
you had customers or users that wanted
您有想要的客户或用户
to use the GPL we would use the open JDK
要使用GPL，我们将使用开放式JDK
builds from from Red Hat so yes it was
来自Red Hat，所以是的
launched in 2006 2007 and then you know
在2006年推出2007年，然后您知道
frankly 2007 to 2009 if you recall that
坦率地说，从2007年到2009年
you're a Sun was struggling a little bit
你是太阳，有点挣扎
so open JDK just kind of floated along
所以打开JDK只是有点像
for a bit but after the acquisition of
有点，但收购后
Sun by Oracle we doubled down
Oracle的Sun，我们的投资翻了一番
aggressively on open JDK so we went to
积极地使用开放式JDK，所以我们去了
Apple who if you recall at that point in
苹果，如果您还记得那时
history had their own separate Java
历史上有各自独立的Java
implementation we went to Apple and said
实施我们去了苹果说
hey why don't you contribute all this to
嘿，你为什么不把这一切都贡献给
open JDK make your your Mac OS ports
打开JDK使您的Mac OS端口
open source and we'll help you with that
开源，我们将为您提供帮助
went went to IBM and say hey why don't
去了IBM，说嘿为什么不
you work with us on open JDK and why
您在开放式JDK上与我们合作，为什么
don't you look at some of the stuff that
你不看一些东西吗
you have and what you know what can be
你有什么，你知道会是什么
open sourced there you have a bunch of
开源那里你有一堆
ports you have your own VM technology
您拥有自己的VM技术的端口
and over the last year or so we've seen
在过去的一年左右的时间里，我们已经看到
IBM open source some of that at eclipse
IBM在Eclipse中开源其中的一些
so that's all good news yeah and then of
所以这都是好消息，然后
course we have dozens and done
当然，我们已经完成了许多工作
sorry dozens and dozens and hundreds of
对不起，成千上万
companies and individual contributors
公司和个人贡献者
that have
具有
participated and are participating in
参加并且正在参加
openjdk the latest trend of course is we
openjdk的最新趋势当然是我们
have a pretty much every cloud vendor
几乎每个云供应商都有
participating in one way or another so
以一种或另一种方式参与
just a few months ago Amazon signed up
就在几个月前，亚马逊签约了
and they have a team that's doing open
他们有一支开放的团队
JDK builds they've already contributed
他们已经贡献的JDK构建
some high quality patches around Mac OS
Mac OS周围的一些高质量补丁
port stuff that they had for their own
他们自己拥有的东西
internal fixes for their own internal
自己内部的内部修复
uses and have included that so it's very
用途并包含了这一点，因此非常
promising and it's you know like I say
有前途，你知道我说的那样
it's over the last 11 years it's done
已经过去了11年
nothing but accelerate which is all good
只不过加速就好了
so just to kind of look at the the open
所以只是看开放
JDK cycle kind of the virtuous cycle of
JDK循环的良性循环
what makes this work is oh is this
是什么让这个工作是这个哦
automatically animating ok anyway so
无论如何会自动设置动画
yeah so we so we start off with the open
是的，所以我们从开放开始
JDK project and again we used to think
在JDK项目中，我们曾经想过
of this more as a place the place where
这更多是一个地方
we had the the source code repos and the
我们有源代码存储库和
governance board and you know we had
治理委员会，你知道我们有
various roles that were defined and so
定义的各种角色等等
on and so forth and and ultimately these
等等，最终这些
projects would work towards creating the
项目将致力于创建
reference implementation so JDK 7 JDK 8
参考实现，因此JDK 7 JDK 8
JDK nine the reference implementation
JDK九参考实现
all came from open JDK builds that were
全部来自于开放的JDK构建
collaboratively worked on with you know
与您共同合作
Oracle Red Hat and and others so we do
Oracle Red Hat和其他人，所以我们这样做
that but that's just a one-time thing
那不过是一回事
right the reference implementation is
正确的参考实现是
just a moment in time but that source
只是片刻而已
code gets consumed by a lot of
代码被很多人消耗
organizations right and you may know
组织的权利，你可能知道
especially if you're an application
特别是如果您是应用程序
developer you may know of the Oracle JDK
您可能认识的Oracle JDK开发人员
which is based on open JDK source code
基于开放的JDK源代码
you may know of the IBM Java SDK you may
您可能知道IBM Java SDK
know of Red Hat's builds you may know if
了解Red Hat的版本，您可能知道
a Xul's builds you may know of Souza's
您可能知道苏扎（Souza）的Xul建筑
builds and Canonical's builds of
和Canonical的
Neuros builds and right so we have all
神经建立，正确，所以我们拥有了所有
these different foundations and groups
这些不同的基金会和团体
and companies working on these builds
和从事这些建设的公司
but what you may not realize is that
但是你可能没有意识到的是
there are a lot of companies that have
有很多公司有
taken the OpenJDK source code and
取得了OpenJDK源代码并
created their own very niche port or
创建了自己的利基港口或
fork of openjdk for internal use so
内部使用openjdk的前叉
Twitter for example they have open JDK
例如Twitter，他们已经打开了JDK
but you would as a java application
但是您将作为Java应用程序
developer you may never recognize what
开发人员，您可能永远不会意识到
it is that they do because you know
他们这样做是因为你知道
they're working on terabytes sized heaps
他们正在处理TB级的堆
right so they have very special very
对，所以他们有非常特别的
customized niche niche code that they're
他们是定制的利基利基代码
using internally and there's a lot of
内部使用，有很多
companies that do that so at JavaOne
JavaOne这样做的公司
this year we had Alibaba who who came
今年我们有阿里巴巴来
and talked about some of the stuff that
并谈到了一些
they're doing which is in a similar vein
他们正在做的事情与此类似
so and then so basically you know all
所以基本上，你知道所有
these organizations and participants end
这些组织和参与者结束了
up feeding back into to open JDK we end
回馈以打开JDK，我们结束了
up with this virtuous cycle there's 12
在这个良性循环中，有12个
million developers using Java so that
百万开发人员使用Java，
creates a strong and stable ecosystem
创建一个强大而稳定的生态系统
all right so basically open JDK current
好的，所以基本上可以打开当前的JDK
status is there's you know a clear
状态在那里你知道一个清楚的
commitment from Oracle post Sun
Oracle对Sun的承诺
acquisition we've lived up to that in a
收购，我们已经实现了这一目标
big way over the last 10 years it's been
在过去的十年中，
seven years I guess since the
我猜是七年了
acquisition and just this summer we we
收购，而就在今年夏天，我们
announced in a Java one we we had a
在Java中宣布我们有一个
keynote pretty much devoted to this
主题演讲非常专注于此
where you know for a long time we've had
你知道我们已经有很长时间了
the Oracle JDK and then other vendors
Oracle JDK然后是其他供应商
have built open JDK binaries and the
建立了开放的JDK二进制文件，并且
Oracle JDK always had some extra pieces
Oracle JDK总是有一些额外的功能
in it that had that were commercial
在其中具有商业意义
right so we had flight recorder Mission
对，所以我们有飞行记录仪任务
Control we had we had been working on
我们一直在努力的控制
some deterministic garbage collection
确定性垃圾回收
technology we had ahead of time
我们提前拥有的技术
compilation stuff that we had been
我们一直在编辑的东西
working on with an AI to commercialize
与AI合作进行商业化
that
那
but basically over the summer just
但基本上是整个夏天
looking at the ecosystem and looking at
看生态系统，看
modern application development and and
现代应用程序开发和
what what especially looking forward to
什么特别期待
cloud development and what developers
云开发以及哪些开发人员
expect we just looked at all that and
希望我们只是看了所有这些并且
said we need to simplify this right so
说我们需要简化这项权利，所以
let's let's not have this separate
让我们不要分开
Oracle JDK and and then other people
Oracle JDK，然后是其他人
with the open JDK binary slits open
打开JDK二进制缝隙
source all this stuff that we've been
采购我们一直以来的所有这些东西
working on and let's increase the
正在努力，让我们增加
release cadence so I'll go through in a
释放节奏，这样我将经历
lot of detail the new release cadence
新发布节奏的很多细节
and how you can kind of form a mental
以及如何形成一种心理
model around how that works versus how
围绕其工作方式与方式进行建模
we used to do things in the past but
我们过去曾经做过的事情，但是
basically you know we're tripling down I
基本上你知道我们要三倍
guess in open JDK as is what I'm saying
我在说开放JDK中的猜测
here so we're gonna start producing open
在这里，我们将开始生产开放
JDK builds and it's going to include all
JDK构建，它将包括所有
of the stuff that we had had as a
我们曾经拥有的东西
separate commercial feature in the past
过去的独立商业功能
all right am i doing for time still 20
好吧，我还是在做时间20
minutes right yeah okay good so we're
分钟，对，好的，所以我们
good on time so yeah so I have two
准时，所以我有两个
daughters and they love really really
女儿，他们真的很喜欢
corny corny jokes and so they're the
坏话，坏话，所以他们是
inspiration for me to try to insert some
启发我尝试插入一些
really corny jokes into presentation so
真的很老套
let's start knock knock oh yeah okay so
让我们开始敲敲敲击哦，是的，所以
just you know not to put you guys down
只是你知道不要让你们失望
or anything but I did this same talk in
或其他任何事情，但我也做了同样的演讲
Jax London a couple of weeks ago when I
几周前当我来到Jax London时
said knock knock they said who's there
说敲敲打他们说谁在那里
like instantly loud so it's still 2 or
像是瞬间响亮，所以仍然是2或
still too early in the morning so let's
还是太早了，让我们
try this again knock knock
再试一次
there we go okay that's better who's
那我们去吧，那是更好的
there all right
那里好
yeah that's a platform Monday yeah so
是的，星期一是一个平台，所以
that's how it's been right that's how
那是正确的这是正确的
it's been since if you look at the
这是因为如果你看
average time between Java SE releases
Java SE版本之间的平均时间
going back to the 1/2 time frame Java
回到1/2时间框架的Java
1/2 so like 98 or so it's a bit on
1/2等于98左右
average 30 to 34 months between major
重大之间平均30到34个月
releases which you know what at the time
发布您当时知道的内容
I think made perfect sense and even five
我认为很合理，甚至五个
years ago I think it made perfect sense
多年前，我认为这很合理
but that is just not how modern
但这不是现代
application development is done anymore
应用程序开发已完成
we simply cannot have long pauses
我们根本不能长时间停顿
between new feature availability right
在新功能可用权之间
I'm jumping ahead I guess but alright
我想我要向前走，但是还好
one more joke what do you get when you
再开一个玩笑，你会得到什么
cross open source and a paddleboat a
跨开源和一艘明轮船
good new canoe yeah and so the point of
好新皮划艇，是的，所以
this joke is is to highlight that again
这个笑话是为了再次强调
modern application developers expect
现代应用程序开发人员期望
everything in their stack or if their
堆栈中的所有内容，或者
stack lists everything in their
堆栈列出了他们的所有内容
stockless stack to be open source right
无库存的堆栈是开源的权利
and and under and easy to use broadly
以及易于使用和广泛使用
used familiar open source license right
使用熟悉的开源许可证权利
alright so just as Java is logo has
好吧，就像Java是徽标一样
transitioned to keep up with the times
过渡以跟上时代
over the last 21 years
在过去的21年中
believe it or not 21 years so shall our
信不信由你21年，我们的信徒
the way we think about builds and
我们对构建的思考方式和
releases now I'm about to go through a
现在发布，我将要经历一个
few slides that I'm going to mentally
我会在头脑中放一些幻灯片
just for the sake of simplicity think of
只是为了简单起见
open JDK and the Oracle JDK is the same
打开JDK和Oracle JDK是一样的
thing and then I promise at the end
事情，然后我保证最后
they'll split it out okay so that you
他们会把它分开，这样你
can kind of see what I mean by Oracle
可以看出我对Oracle的意思
JDK it opens you decay and I know for
JDK它使您衰减，我知道
some people they only think of the
有些人他们只会想到
Oracle JDK when they think
他们思考Oracle JDK时
of java SE and i know some people get
SE的代码，我知道有人
frustrated when i talk in a way that
当我以那种方式说话时感到沮丧
presumes that there is only the Oracle
假定只有甲骨文
JDK and that there's not all these other
JDK，还有其他所有这些
really good open JDK builds so I'm just
真正好的开放JDK构建，所以我只是
gonna be upfront about that so just bear
会提前，所以忍受
with me and I'll separate it at the end
和我在一起，我会在最后分开
alright so again Oracle is going to
好了，Oracle再一次将
start to produce open JDK builds our
开始生产开放的JDK构建我们的
goal is that open JDK binary has become
目标是开放的JDK二进制文件已成为
completely interchangeable with Oracle
与Oracle完全可互换
JDK binaries we in the Java platform
我们在Java平台中的JDK二进制文件
group at Oracle have never really liked
Oracle的团队从未真正喜欢过
it that it's been difficult for
它很难
developers to go between open JDK
开发人员之间打开JDK
binaries and Oracle JDK binaries and it
二进制文件和Oracle JDK二进制文件及其
is difficult there are some differences
很难有一些差异
we want to get rid of that entirely and
我们想完全摆脱它，
I don't just mean the commercial
我不只是说广告
features I mean there's always been
功能，我的意思是一直存在
little idiosyncrasies especially if you
小特质，特别是如果你
have a race condition happy type
有种族条件的幸福型
application it's always been a challenge
应用程序一直是一个挑战
to move back and forth so we're gonna
来回移动，所以我们要
try to reduce that and eliminate it
尝试减少并消除它
completely alright so let's look at the
完全没问题，让我们看一下
release model and let's look at kind of
发布模型，让我们看一下
the let's look at like a historical
让我们看一下历史
perspective of it so the goal was always
因此，目标始终是
every two years right like we always did
每两年一次，就像我们一如既往
even going back to the Sun II always
甚至总是回到太阳II
tried to have a two year release cadence
试图有一个两年的发布节奏
and yes it was usually closer to three
是的，通常接近三
but just for the sake of the mental
只是为了精神
model going forward let's presume we had
继续前进的模型让我们假设我们有
said we're gonna keep doing the old way
说我们要继续做旧
of every two years okay so let's zoom in
每两年还可以，所以让我们放大
on that a little bit now you can go and
在那一点上，现在你可以去
look at the release history so on Java
查看Java的发行历史
comm we actually just Google for Java SE
通讯，我们实际上只是Google for Java SE
release history and you'll find a page
发布历史记录，您会找到一个页面
that shows you the release of every date
向您显示每个日期的发布
the the date of every release and what
每次发布的日期以及什么
you'll notice is for Java 7 and Java 8
您会注意到它适用于Java 7和Java 8
we actually had a six-month release
我们实际上有六个月的发布时间
cadence of feature updates within those
这些功能更新的节奏
major releases so when we released Java
主要版本，所以当我们发布Java时
7 six months later we had a seven update
7个六个月后，我们进行了七个更新
that had new features in it and when and
具有新功能以及何时和
then six months after that there was
然后六个月之后
another one that had
另一个有
true new features in it okay so we have
真正的新功能好吧，所以我们有
a history of doing six months feature
做六个月的历史
updates it's been there for many many
更新了很多很多
years so if we were to look forward
年，所以如果我们期待
using the old semantics we would say
使用旧的语义，我们会说
okay so we'll have nine and six months
好吧，我们有九六个月
we'll have nine one and 92 and 93 and
我们将有9个和92和93
then a couple years out we'll get into
然后几年，我们将进入
ten and so on and so forth but what if
十等等等等，但是如果
we look at this a little bit differently
我们对此有所不同
okay and one of the things we struggled
好的，我们挣扎的事情之一
with is yes in every six months we had a
每六个月就有一次
feature we had new features but we could
功能我们有新功能，但我们可以
never introduce a feature that required
从不引入所需的功能
working with the JCP and updating the
与JCP合作并更新
specification so we were doing six-month
规范，所以我们做了六个月
feature updates but we were never able
功能更新，但我们从未能够
to introduce a new language feature or
引入新的语言功能或
change an API that was part of the
更改属于
specification so we we would kind of get
规范，所以我们会得到
stuck in the types of things we could
卡在我们可以做的事情中
update every six months so what if we
每六个月更新一次，如果我们
blow that up and we've been working with
炸毁，我们一直在与
the JCP for almost a year now to
JCP已经快一年了
streamline how how you know how we go
简化您如何知道我们的前进方式
through the spec processes and we've
通过规格流程，我们已经
said hey then this and again this been
说嘿然后这又是
for a year discussed at the JCP there's
在JCP讨论了一年的时间
a working group about having the sorry
一个对不起的工作组
having openjdk and the JCP processes
具有openjdk和JCP流程
work together in a nice way
很好地合作
what if we can may expect changes on the
如果我们可以预期会发生什么变化呢？
go so so for example in 9.1 what if we
例如，在9.1中
could introduce type inference like what
可以像什么介绍类型推断
if we could put some type inferencing in
如果我们可以在其中添加一些类型推断
or change a little bit about how we do
或改变一下我们的做法
enum to make so you can put class types
进行枚举，以便您可以放置​​类类型
in there or there was you know
在那儿或那里你知道
underscore was made a reserved word so
下划线是保留字，因此
there's can we put that in tool and it's
我们可以将其放入工具中
like so these are things that we would
就像这些，我们会
normally would have had to wait two
通常本来要等两个
years to be able to do that we can now
多年才能做到的，我们现在可以
do on six-month cadence and those things
做六个月的节奏和那些事情
I just said by the way are proposed for
我只是说是建议
that next release okay so we need so we
那下一个版本好吧，所以我们需要，所以我们
have a new way of thinking about
有新的思考方式
releases okay so yeah we were always
发布好了，是的，我们一直
doing six months
做六个月
updates we had always been doing
我们一直在做的更新
six-month updates but now we're saying
六个月的更新，但现在我们要说的是
let's be able to let's make it so we're
让我们能够做到，所以我们
able to do six-month updates that we can
能够进行六个月的更新，我们可以
get into the spec stuff how many minutes
进入规格书多少分钟
don't have 15 that doesn't sound right
没有15个听起来不正确的
when did I start really I 15 then 30 but
我什么时候开始真正的我15然后30
I have 35 minutes okay that's good all
我有35分钟可以，很好
right yeah so so because we're gonna
是的，所以是这样，因为我们要
kind of blow up the way we think about
炸毁了我们的思考方式
these six-month releases one of the
这六个月的发行版之一
things we want to do is blow up the way
我们想要做的事情就是炸毁方式
like we need to shift people's mental
就像我们需要改变人们的思想
model around this stuff and so one of
围绕这个东西建模，所以其中之一
the greatest ways to shift people's
改变人们的最大方式
mental models is to create a huge bike
心理模型是创造一辆巨大的自行车
shed right and so what we've proposed is
摆脱权利，所以我们建议的是
that we're gonna change the versioning
我们将要更改版本
number the version numbering to a year
将版本编号编号为一年
dot month and we're so we're gonna do
世界末日，所以我们要做
six-month releases in March on September
九月的三月发布六个月
and we're going to instead of going nine
而我们要去而不是去九
10 11 or 9.1 9.2 we're going to go your
10 11或9.1 9.2我们将继续
dot month right so that people can in
正确的点月，以便人们可以
their mind separate the old way from the
他们的思想将旧方法与
new way right so we'll have people that
正确的新方法，这样我们就会有一些人
like let's face it there will be people
就像面对现实一样
using arch grandchildren will be using
使用大孙子将使用
Java 8 I'm positive of that right Java 8
Java 8我对Java 8持肯定态度
is gonna be around for a very long time
将会存在很长一段时间
just like Java 6 was around for a very
就像Java 6诞生了
long time and so but I so I want a way
等了很久，但是我想要一个方法
for people to kind of shift their mental
使人们改变思维方式
model between the old way and the new
在旧方法与新方法之间建立模型
way of doing things so that's why we've
做事的方式，这就是为什么我们
proposed this year dot month versioning
提议今年点月版本控制
scheme so that that we get into this
方案，以便我们进入这个
kind of clear perception that ok yeah we
那种清楚的感觉，好吧，我们
have six month releases this is the new
有六个月的发布，这是新的
way of doing things ok now if you are a
现在做事的方式，如果你是一个
enterprise and you're one of those
企业，你就是其中之一
companies that has said holy crap every
曾经说过废话的公司
three years is way too fast like can't
三年太快了，就像不能
you guys slow this down and do a release
你们放慢脚步，然后发布
every five
每五个
and we believe it or not we get that
我们信不信由你
right like half of the time I get
就像我有一半的时间
feedback on release cadence half of it
关于发布节奏的反馈
is you're going way too fast and half of
你走得太快了一半
it is you're going way too slow which
是你走得太慢了
probably means we're in the Goldilocks
可能意味着我们在Goldilocks
zone right so what we want to do though
正确的区域，所以我们想做什么
is modern application developers which
是现代应用程序开发人员
are taking over the world and is where
正在占领世界，并且在那里
all the growth is are you know expect
所有的增长都是你知道的吗
six-month releases like that that's
这样六个月的发行是
unquestioned but we don't want to blow
毫无疑问，但我们不想吹
up how people consume and develop their
人们如何消费和发展他们的
applications so what we're gonna do is
应用程序，所以我们要做的是
just like we had done in the past like
就像我们过去所做的一样
you can think about a major the old
你可以考虑一个大的老
major release let's shift the thinking
主要版本让我们改变思维
of that a little bit and just call those
其中的一点，只是打电话给那些
long-term support releases and so the
长期支持发布，因此
first long-term support release we've
我们发布的第一个长期支持版本
proposed is going to be 18.9 so that's
建议的将是18.9，所以
next September
明年九月
and you may think oh my gosh nine is not
你可能会认为哦，我的天哪九不是
a long-term support release it's like
长期支持发布就像
well no what if I was to say that was
好吧，如果我要说那是
nine and nine u xx and nine use 40 was
九和九u xx和九使用40是
going to be the long-term support
将是长期的支持
release nobody would bat an eye
释放没有人会注视
everybody go well yeah that makes sense
每个人都很好，这是有道理的
because that's what we did for seven
因为那是我们七年来所做的
that's what we did for eight right when
那就是我们在八小时之内所做的
we released eight we did eight update 20
我们发布了八个更新，我们做了八个更新20
and then we would never support you on
然后我们永远都不会支持您
eight if you want to support you need it
八，如果你想支持，你需要它
to be
成为
you need to reproduce the problem in
您需要重现该问题
eight u xx and then when we released
八个u xx，然后当我们释放时
eight u 40 you needed to reproduce the
八个u 40您需要重现
issue in eight u 40 we were never gonna
在八四十中我们永远都不会
support you in eight u 20 right same
在八个你20正确的支持你
thing here okay what we're saying is
这里的事情好吧，我们所说的是
work on nine when 18.3 comes out work on
当18.3出来时，在9点上工作
18.3 when 18.9 comes out work on 18.9
18.3当18.9出现时，在18.9上工作
and then good news 18.9 will have five
然后好消息18.9将有五个
years at least of nothing but security
年至少无非是安全
and stability updates there'll be no new
和稳定性更新，不会有新的
features so if you're an enterprise you
功能，因此，如果您是企业，
would go from eight to 18.9 and you'd
从8变到18.9
have a five-year release and I have a
有五年的发布时间，而我有一个
picture here that'll kind of show all
这里的图片会显示全部
that in line alright so the goal is
好的，所以目标是
every three years or so and this you
每三年左右，这个你
know this can change
知道这可以改变
depending on what's happening in the
取决于发生的事情
ecosystem or if there's some incredibly
生态系统，或者是否有令人难以置信的
major new feature that comes in and we
主要的新功能出现了，我们
say you know what we'd like to give that
说你知道我们想要给什么
six more months to bake before we call
我们打电话之前要再烘烤六个月
it a long term support release so we can
它是长期支持版本，因此我们可以
tweak that a little bit but roughly the
稍微调整一下，但大致
goal is every three years we have
我们的目标是每三年
roughly five years of long-term support
大约五年的长期支持
which gives you lots of time to move
这给你很多时间移动
between the major releases just as you
与您一样在主要版本之间
always have right and so when I was
总是有权利，所以当我
talking about this in Jack's London a
在杰克的伦敦谈论这个
couple weeks ago which is mostly
几个星期前
financial industry people when I started
我刚开始从事金融业的人
talking about the first part you could
谈论你可以做的第一部分
see the stress on everybody's eyes like
看到每个人的眼睛上的压力
whole how are we gonna keep up with six
整个我们该如何跟上六个
months releases this is gonna be a
月发布，这将是一个
disaster
灾害
and then when I put this up you could
然后当我把它放好时
just see the relief right it's like okay
只是看到救济就好了
so what you're saying is for me nothing
所以你说的对我来说什么都没有
has to change right I can just like wake
必须改变权利，我就像唤醒
me when the next long-term support
我当下长期支持
designated release comes along and by
指定的发布会随之而来
the way this model sorry just one sec
这个模型对不起一秒钟的方式
this model is like this isn't like some
这个模型就像这样不像某些
thing that we invented a thin hair this
我们发明了稀疏的头发的东西
is a model that works very well for a
是一种非常适合
number of open-source projects and
开源项目的数量和
platforms yes sorry yeah I'll I'll talk
平台是的，抱歉，我会说
about that so our timeline for aid is
关于这一点，我们的援助时间表是
2025 as of now but I wasn't joking when
截至目前的2025年，但我当时还没有开玩笑
I said like my grandkids we will
我说过像孙子一样
probably be supporting that actually the
可能会支持实际上
probably the biggest hindrance to I was
可能对我最大的障碍是
talking with somebody at breakfast about
早餐时和某人聊天
this though the biggest hindrance I
这虽然是我最大的障碍
think to the lifetime of aid is going to
想一生的援助将
be the 32-bit rollover problem in what's
是什么的32位翻转问题
that twenty thirty eight yeah so that's
那二十八是啊，那是
somebody's gonna have some work to do on
某人要做一些工作
that one my kids alright okay so now
我的一个孩子还好吧，现在
let's so let's in line here the the
让我们在这里排队
current releases with the like the
当前版本的
future releases right so if JT k6j to
未来的版本是正确的，所以如果JT k6j
k7j decay they're they're rough
k7j衰减，因为它们很粗糙
timelines there and again I'm to be
时间表，我要成为
clear I'm conflating you know the Oracle
清除我在混淆您知道Oracle
JDK you know paid support option
您知道的JDK付费支持选项
timeline here with what is in open G
这里的时间线与开放G中的内容
okay and who is working on that right
好的，谁在为此而努力
but like this kind of gives you the
但是像这样给你
perspective of that alright so let now
好的角度，现在让我们
that's overlay like how this looks from
像这样叠加起来
the Oracle JDK perspective so while we
Oracle JDK透视图
are going to start working on open JDK
将开始在开放的JDK上工作
builds it is going to take some time for
建立它需要一些时间
those to be completely interchangeable
那些完全可以互换的
with open JDK right so we need to we
与开放的JDK对，所以我们需要
need to continue to produce the Oracle
需要继续生产甲骨文
JDK as well so for Java 9 for 18 3 and
JDK以及Java 9 for 18 3和
18 9 we will continue to produce an
18 9我们将继续生产
Oracle JDK and open JDK by builds from
Oracle JDK和由以下版本构建的开放式JDK
Oracle and again I would presume I like
甲骨文，我想我也喜欢
I'm I have no idea one way or the other
我不知道一种方法还是另一种方法
but I would presume that Red Hat are
但我认为红帽是
going to continue to produce their open
将继续产生他们的开放
JDK builds as they always have
JDK始终如一地构建
and I would presume that is ool will and
我认为这是愚蠢的意愿，
I would presume that one arrow will keep
我想一个箭头会保持
doing their arm builds and so on and so
做他们的手臂锻炼等等
forth right but yeah so but this shows
正确，但是是的，但这表明
you like from an Oracle perspective
从Oracle角度来看您喜欢
we're not going to go back in time and
我们不会回到过去
produce Oracle is not going to go back
产生甲骨文不会回去
in time and produce open JDK builds for
及时生产开放的JDK构建
8 but I expect Red Hat will continue to
8，但我希望Red Hat会继续
do so
这样做
just as they continue to do so for JDK 6
正如他们继续为JDK 6所做的那样
and JDK 7 right so even when Oracle
和JDK 7对，即使Oracle
takes the Oracle JDK and moves that into
使用Oracle JDK并将其移至
the commercial support offering we have
我们提供的商业支持服务
vendors like Red Hat who come in and
像Red Hat这样的供应商
take that over right and I would expect
把它接过来，我希望
that to continue going forward but you
继续前进，但是你
know we'll see how that goes
知道我们会明白的
now these are also like so I you know
现在这些也一样，所以我你知道
put another way like this slide is
像这样的幻灯片放另一种方式是
Oracle's point of view of this there is
甲骨文对此的观点是
absolutely nothing that would stop
绝对不会停止
anybody any any of the vendors I've
任何人我有任何供应商
mentioned or any individual for that
提到或为此的任何个人
matter to pick any one of these and
重要的是选择其中任何一个
decide that they would like that to have
决定他们希望有
long-term support as well right so this
也有长期的支持，所以这
is just Oracle's perspective and what we
只是Oracle的观点，而我们
are intending to do in this space
打算在这个空间里做
all right so then you know kind of
好吧，那么你就知道了
condensing and condensing it all up
压缩并压缩全部
basically you can see we're going to a
基本上你可以看到我们要去
world where we'll have six month release
我们将有六个月的发布时间
cycles targeting modern application
针对现代应用的循环
development we will continue with six
发展，我们将继续六个
seven and eight as we had and then we're
像我们以前的七点和八点，然后我们
gonna go to a long term support model
会选择长期支持模式
for those enterprises that frankly
对于那些坦率的企业
really liked that long period between
真的很喜欢
releases and application transitions so
发布和应用程序过渡，因此
that was it for my slides I have five
就是我的幻灯片，我有五个
minutes for questions and again I would
分钟的问题，我会再次
just like to remind you I don't hear the
只是想提醒您，我听不到
best so if you have questions speak
最好，如果您有任何疑问，请说
loudly please yes well so yes so
大声请是好，所以是这样
everything okay so the question for
一切都很好，所以这个问题
those in the back that may not have
那些后面可能没有的人
heard was about Java SE embedded and how
听说过有关Java SE嵌入式以及如何
this relates to that so if you actually
这与此有关，如果你实际上
go to the Oracle Java SE embedded page
转到Oracle Java SE嵌入式页面
there's actually a couple of notes there
那里实际上有几个笔记
about this and we also I also published
关于这个，我们也发表了
a blog on this just a few weeks ago the
几周前的博客
Java platform group blog if you just
Java平台组博客，如果您只是
look for Java platform group blog at
在以下位置查找Java平台组博客
Oracle you'll find it so that'll have
Oracle，您会找到它的，以便
more details on what I can say right
我可以说正确的更多细节
here so for those of you that may not
在这里，对于那些可能不会
know we've had a separate commercial
知道我们有一个单独的广告
only embedded build of Java SE it had
它只有Java SE的嵌入式版本
very specialized ports and you could do
非常专业的港口，你可以做
compact profiles okay we open sourced
紧凑的配置文件好了，我们开源了
all of that code all of those ports
所有这些代码所有这些端口
including some
包括一些
mobile hooks about two or three years
移动挂钩大约两三年
ago and we if you look at Jeb and 9 with
以前，如果您看一下Jeb和9
jigsaw the value proposition of compact
拼图契约的价值主张
profiles goes away right so the only
个人资料消失，所以唯一
value is really in the custom ports
价值确实在自定义端口中
right so we've open-sourced all that and
是的，所以我们开源了所有这些，
Oracle is not intending to have a Java
Oracle不想使用Java
SE embedded 9 and later so we still have
SE嵌入了9及更高版本，因此我们仍然拥有
the Java SE embedded 8 but we've put arm
Java SE Embedded 8，但我们已经投入使用
on restricted availability and our
关于有限的可用性和我们的
intent is that the ecosystem is going to
目的是生态系统将
take that over because they largely have
接管那是因为他们在很大程度上
right so there's a couple of vendors the
对，所以有几个供应商
one in particular company called micro
一家特别叫micro的公司
dock and so they they supply ARM based
对接，因此他们提供基于ARM的产品
ports of Java SE embedded on a kind of
嵌入式Java SE的端口
commercial basis but all the source code
商业基础，但所有源代码
is there if anybody wanted to pick this
有没有人要选这个
up and run with it for free under the
并在以下免费运行
GPL yeah so question there yeah yeah so
GPL是的，所以有问题，是的，所以
yeah it's not now
是的，现在不是
so we still have to think about that a
所以我们仍然必须考虑
little bit because like you say the the
因为有点像你说的
challenge is in order to build open jfx
挑战是为了建立开放的jfx
you have to actually build an entire JDK
您必须实际构建整个JDK
with it which is really I'm really
真的，我真的
unfortunate right because what we would
不幸的权利，因为我们会
like is that it's just a separate thing
就像那是一回事
that can be kind of treated separately
可以单独对待
right so we have to figure that out but
对，所以我们必须弄清楚，但是
you know keep in mind that the strategy
你知道记住这个策略
here is really about modern application
这真的是关于现代应用
cloud development right so we need to
云开发正确，所以我们需要
you know at JavaOne we've been talking
你知道在JavaOne我们一直在谈论
to a number of companies and partners
给许多公司和合作伙伴
that may be interested in doing
可能有兴趣做
something with that and looking at the
那个东西，看着
licensing or if we can get in and
许可，或者我们是否可以进入
finally get to making those changes that
最终做出那些改变
have it as a separate module you can
将其作为单独的模块可以
just choose to plug it in or not so I
只是选择插入或不插入，所以我
know it wasn't a yes/no answer but
知道不是肯定/否定答案，但是
it's the best I can do I'm afraid yeah
这是我能做到的最好的，是的
yeah yeah that will not change so we
是的，那不会改变，所以我们
will still have the Oracle JDK it will
仍将拥有Oracle JDK
still have the the same commercial
仍然有相同的广告
feature licensing that's there but the
有功能许可，但是
good news is that sometime within the
好消息是，
next year we're aggressively working to
明年，我们将积极努力
open source that code and put it in our
将该代码开源并将其放入我们的
open JDK builds so you'll have the
开放的JDK构建，因此您将拥有
option to just use that for free under
选择在下面免费使用
the GPL but the Oracle JDK to the degree
GPL，但是Oracle JDK在一定程度上
it exists going forward is going to be a
它的存在将成为未来
separate commercial thing yeah so yeah
独立的商业事物，是的，是的
all right time for one more question
好的时候再问一个问题
well one more question yes yeah it could
还有一个问题是的，可以
be it is no which is you know funny
是不是，你知道这很有趣
enough it's like which is why we padded
足够了，这就是为什么我们填充
all the spaces between the eight years
八年之间的所有空间
like why we went in increments of 20
就像为什么我们以20为增量
right it was so that if things did slip
是的，如果事情确实发生了，
where we had to do an emergency release
我们不得不紧急发布的地方
in the middle or something we could
在中间或我们可以
still keep that but there's lots of
仍然保留，但有很多
wonderful threads on this in the open
公开上的精彩线程
JDK mailing list so Dan and Kurt I would
JDK邮件列表，所以Dan和Kurt我会
encourage you to hop in and participate
鼓励你参加
because like you know honestly like we
因为像你一样诚实地知道我们
do take that stuff very seriously and
确实认真对待这些东西，
but at the same time at the same time
但是在同一时间
like sometimes you gotta you got to
就像有时候你要
knock people in the shoulder a little
稍微敲人的肩膀
bit to change the way you think about
有点改变你的思考方式
how things are being done because this
事情如何进行，因为这
is this is a change this is different
这是变化吗，这是不同的
and it does mean that you know some
这确实意味着您知道一些
people are going to have to do more work
人们将不得不做更多的工作
with their tools and frameworks and
他们的工具和框架，以及
applications than they had to do in the
应用程序比他们在
past and I know that that can be a scary
过去，我知道那可能令人恐惧
proposition when you're always resource
总是有资源时的命题
constrained
受约束的
but I think in order to keep up with
但我想为了跟上
modern application development like this
像这样的现代应用程序开发
is a requirement so and I think we're at
是一个要求，所以我认为我们在
a time I'm feel free to kind of catch me
有一次我可以随时抓住我
while I'm packing up my computer but I
我收拾电脑时，但我
don't want to abuse the extra couple
不想滥用多余的情侣
minutes we had so all right thanks a lot
分钟，我们非常感谢，非常感谢
appreciate it
欣赏它
[Applause]
[掌声]